(Leonard:)...at the Topical Conference
on Bose-Einstein Condensates.
(Sheldon:)I know. I read it before I threw it out.
Okay, if I may drill down
to the bedrock of my question...
...why did you throw it out?
(Sheldon:)Because I have no interest in standing in
the Rose Room of the Pasadena Marriott...
(Sheldon:)...in front of a group
of judgmental strangers...
...who wouldn't recognize genius if it were
standing in front of them giving a speech.
(Sheldon:)Which, if I were there, it would be.
(Howard:)I don't know, Sheldon.
Those Topical Conference on Bose-Einstein
Condensates parties are legendary.
(Leonard:)Forget the parties.
(Howard:)Forget the parties? What a nerd.
Any other honors I've gotten
that I don't know about?
(Leonard:)Did UPS drop off a Nobel Prize
with my name on it?
Leonard, don't take this the wrong way,
but the day you win a Nobel Prize...
(Sheldon:)...is the day I begin my research on the
drag coefficient of tassels on flying carpets.
Ha, ha, ha. The only thing missing from
that insult was your mama.
I got one. Hey, Leonard, your mama's
research methodology is so flawed...
(Leonard:)Shut up, Howard.